(Sheldon:)Although as I say this,
(Sheldon:)that might not have been
what you were asking.
(Leonard:)You think they'll
still go on the trip?
(Sheldon:)All I know is after the fight
I went to Emily's to smooth...
(Leonard:)They're not going on the trip.
No.
(Raj:)What is wrong with you?
(Sheldon:)Look at him, caring about
what's wrong with me.
(Sheldon:)That is some top-shelf empathy.
(Sheldon:)Hey, well,
we should start a club.
(Raj:)You went to Emily's
to apologize.
(Raj:)And when you left,
she was crying.
(Sheldon:)That is true.
(Sheldon:)Well, I suppose
I should apologize again.
(all saying no)
(Penny:)Is she okay?
(Raj:)Yeah, I calmed her down.
(Raj:)But she's not going
to Vegas if he's going.
(Howard:)Wait, that's an option?
(Howard:)I didn't know that
was an option.
(Sheldon:)Well, that is fine,
because I've decided
(Sheldon:)that I won't be joining you.
(Sheldon:)I've realized that
the most genuine way
(Sheldon:)to demonstrate the remorse
I feel is to let you
(Sheldon:)have this weekend
to yourselves.